<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Sahil's Blog</title><link>https://sahilunagar.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Sahil's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sahilunagar.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://sahilunagar.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://sahilunagar.github.io/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml ``` [outputs] home = [&amp;ldquo;HTML&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;JSON&amp;rdquo;] ```</description></item><item><title>Deep Learning for Image Classification</title><link>https://sahilunagar.github.io/posts/deep-learning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://sahilunagar.github.io/posts/deep-learning/</guid><description>This post covers what Deep Learning, Image Classification and Convolutional Neural Networks are:
In the era of Big data where Deep Learning algorithms can extract patterns from data that even human cannot find, there are problems in which even these algorithms tend to perform worse than expectations. I worked on a Computer Vision problem, in which the aim was to build and analyse a Deep Learning model for image identification.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://sahilunagar.github.io/posts/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://sahilunagar.github.io/posts/introduction/</guid><description>Greeting! This is an introduction post. This post tests the followings:
Hero image is in the same directory as the post. This post should be at top of the sidebar. Post author should be the same as specified in author.yaml file.</description></item></channel></rss>